A Guide to the Louis Arthur Johnson Papers, ca. 1930-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series V. Papers of the Secretary of Defense
  - Subseries A, General Correspondence
    - Correspondence with General Carl A. Spaatz 1949-1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with C. Lee Spillers 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Harley O. Staggers, Congressman 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Ingram M. Stainback 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Laurence A. Steinhardt, American Embassy, Canada 1949-1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Edward R. Stettinius 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Irvin Stewart 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Isaac M. Stewart, Union Carbine and Carbon Corp. 1949-1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Wm. Stewart 1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Henry L. Stimson 1949-1950 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Arthur Hays Sulzberger, the New York Times 1949 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Admiral C. A. Swanson (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Charles Sweeny (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Herbert Bayard Swope (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with W. Stuart Symington, Dept. of the Air Force (Box 109)
    - Correspondence with Henry J. Taylor 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Myron C. Taylor 1950 (Box 110)
    - Memorandum re: Tentative Legislative Program for the Department of Defense for 1951 1950 Sept. 1 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Mollie Thayer 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with L. Newton Thomas 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Walter Thurmond 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Louis B. Tim 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Maurice J. Tobin, Secretary of Labor 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Harry Aubrey Toulmin, Jr. 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with James W. Trimble 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with President Harry Truman, includes correspondence from various other people as enclosures 1949 Feb. 5-1950 Sept. 5 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with President Harry Truman 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Millard E. Tydings, Senator, Chairman, Committee on Armed Services 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with James B. Underwood 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with A. H. Vandenberg, Senator 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Cornelius Vanderbilt 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with James K. Vardaman, Jr., Board of Governors, Federal Reserve System 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Major General Harry H. Vaughan 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Bruce Vickers 1950 Aug. (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Carl Vinson, Chairman, Committee on Armed Services, House of Representatives 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Memorandum re: Carl Vinson statement before the House of Representatives re: strength of Armed Forces 1950 July 25-26 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Tracy S. Voorhers 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with John M. Vorys, House of Representatives 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with James E. Webb, the Under Secretary of State 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with William Webster 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Sumner Wells, former Under Secretary of State 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with A. L. Wenner-Gren 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Compton I. White, Congressman 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Rev. Robert J. White 1949-1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Roy B. White, The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co. 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Joseph S. Whiteford 1950 Aug. (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. A. F. Whitney 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Cornelius Vanderbilt Whitney 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Robert E. Wilson 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Walter Winchell 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with J. M. Wolfe 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Matthew Woll, American Federation of Labor 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Lyttleton W. Wood 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with General R. E. Wood, Sears, Roebuck and Co. 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Roy O. Woodruff 1949 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with Stanley Woodward 1950 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence with W. H. Worrilow, Lebannon Steel Foundry 1949 (Box 110)
    - Calling Cards list 1949 (Box 111)
    - Directives, for various departments and government heads, 3 folders 1949 Dec.-1950 Sept. 18 (Box 111)
    - Disposition Form 1949-1950 (Box 111)
    - List of items taken to Cabinet Meeting 1949 June 10 (Box 111)
    - List of persons primarily responsible for the preparation of the budget 1950 (Box 111)
    - List of the Secretary of Defense's Official and Out-of-Town Engagements 1949-1950 (Box 111)
    - Messages and Statements 1949 March-Sept. (Box 111)
    - Messages and Statements, 3 folders 1949 Oct.-1950 Sept. 19 (Box 112)
    - Printed Material, "A Scientific Pilot Training Plan," Link Aviation, Inc., prepared by E. O. Carmody 1948 (Box 112)
    - Statements before Congressional Committee 1950 (Box 112)
    - Correspondence, Commendatory Mail re: Johnson's Resignation, A-H, 4 folders 1950 Sept.-Oct. (Box 113)
    - Correspondence, Commendatory Mail re: Johnson's Resignation, I-R, 5 folders 1950 Sept.-Nov. (Box 114)
    - Correspondence, Commendatory Mail re: Johnson's Resignation, S-Z, 3 folders 1950 Sept.-Nov., 1951 Jan. (Box 115)
    - First and final drafts of Louis Johnson's letter of resignation as Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept. 12 (Box 115)
    - Correspondence re: Johnson's resignation as Secretary of Defense, taken from 2 scrapbooks, 2 folders 1950 Sept. (Box 115)
    - Correspondence re: Johnson's resignation as Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept.-Oct. (Box 115)
    - Letters of appreciation by Louis Johnson upon the occasion of his resignation as Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept. (Box 115)
    - Correspondence with John B. Adams 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memorandum re: Russell Adams, member Civil Aeronautics Board 1949 (Box 116)
    - "Agenda" of things to take up with the President 1949 May-June (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with H. W. Alden 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Archibald S. Alexander, Under Secretary of the Army 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: the first Armed Forces Day 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Wm. R. Arnold 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: M. H. Aylesworth 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Edward A. Bacon 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Ernest L. Bailey 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Frank Bane 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: J. R. Barefoot 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Randy H. Barnard 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Lt. Col. Thomas M. Barton 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Morgan Beatty 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with John Bennett 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Adolf Berle 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Peter Berry 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with John E. Bierwirth 1949-1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Samuel W. Bishop 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Paul Bissinger 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Jacob Blanstein 1949-1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. O. L. Bodenhamer 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with A. G. Boesel 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Frances Bolton 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Edwin Bond 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Commodore Pedro Borges 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Nassos Botsis 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: the Boy Scouts 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Eldred Brandon 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Lyon W. Brandon 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Owen Brewster, Senator 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Edgar A. Broan 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Walter Buchanan 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Clayton R. Burt 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with John Carroll 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Amon G. Carter 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with M. E. Carver 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with C. L. Chennault 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Brooks Claxton 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Mr. Charles Coates 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Ross A. Collins 1949-1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Grover Combs 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Phil Conley 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Clifford D. Cooper 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Herbert Corey [1950] (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Courtesy Calls 1949 April 18 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Leo T. Crowley 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Wm. R. Daley 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Marshall N. Dana 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with J. W. Davis 1949-1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Thomas Delzell 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Admiral Sir Cyril E. Douglas-Pennant 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Lewsi W. Douglas 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Frances Drake, Roving Editor, Reader's Digest1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Wm. W. Drummey 1949 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: Mr. Durga-Das 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Richard Durham 1949 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Governor George Earle 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Walter Ernst 1950 (Box 116)
    - Memo re: [Melik] Esenbel 1950 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence with Abraham Feinberg 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Doris Fleeson 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Robert D. Flory 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Henry Ford, II 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Cedric Foster 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with James D. Francis 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Jack Franklin 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Admiral Fraser 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: French Chiefs of Staff 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Earl E. Gangewere 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Fraser S. Gardner 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Frank Gigliotti 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with A. Robert Ginsburgh 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with J. M. Gordon 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with John Gunther 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with E. K. Haibach 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with John M. Hall 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Jake Halsted 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: General Thomas T. Handy 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with David A. Harrison 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Horace Heidt 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Col. A. W. Herrington 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Randal Heymanson re: Sir Keith Murdoch 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with M. J. Hickey 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with W. A. Higinbotham 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence re: Harry W. Hill 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Col. Howard G. Hill 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with J. H. Hoeppel 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Homer A. Holt 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Jackson Holtz 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Harold Horan 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Arthur A. de la Houssaye 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with D. K. Howe 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with F. S. Hugill 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: R. A. Hummel 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Vice Admiral G. F. Hussey 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Wm. A. Hyman 1949 (Box 117)
    - wanted to schedule for meetings 1949 March (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Interfaith in Action Gold Medal 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Introduction to Group of 27 College Professors from the American University [1949?] (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Col. Charles Johnson 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Erwin Johnson 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Catesby L. Jones 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with George S. Jones 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Robert Jones 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Sam H. Jones 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with W. Alton Jones 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with R. M. Kant 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Irving R. Kaufman 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Clark Kee 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: James S. Kemper 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Robert Kent 1950 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Liaquat Ali Khan 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with George Killion 1949-1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with J. R. Kinder 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with S. R. Kirkpatrick 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Wm. Kloepfer, the Times Herald1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Ambassador Koo 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Col. Kenneth Kreps 1950 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Arthur F. Kroeger 1949 (Box 117)
    - Memo re: Dr. Joseph Ker 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Laurence S. Kuter, Major General, re: MATS 1949 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence with Chester H. Lang 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Felix Larkin, General Counsel, Office of Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept. (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with George A. LaVallee 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Robert A. Learnard 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Marx Leva 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Anthony Leviero, N. Y. Times and Sidney Shalett, Saturday Evening Post1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Lt. General Gilberto R. Limon, Secretary of Defense, Mexico 1950 (Box 118)
    - Lists of Senators and Congressmen invited to briefings 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Al Lodwick 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Edward V. Laughlin 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Mr. Hugh Love of Travelers' Insurance Co. 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Carson F. Lyman 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Mr. McDonald 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Captain F. L. McGaha 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. James McGranery 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Gilbert MacKay 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Clinton D. McKinnon 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: General James F. McManmon 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Joseph T. McNarney, Office of Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept. (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with General John Magruder 1950 Sept. (Box 118)
    - Memo re: B. Majewski 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Lester Markel 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Jackson Matthews 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Roy James Mayo 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Merrill C. Meigs 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Edwin B. Meissner 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Izetta Jewel Miller 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Ray T. Miller 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with E. A. Mobley 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Henry S. Moser 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with S. C. Moody 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with B. F. Moomaw 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with James E. Mooney 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Lewis J. Moorman 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Eunice Morris 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Stanley C. Morris 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: C. F. Morrison 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Walter Munro 1949-1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with A. S. Murphy 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: National Association of Manufacturers, Gov. Relations Advisory Committee 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Elliott Newcomb 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Lloyd Norman, Chicago Tribune1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: the recording for Congressman O'Hara 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with John H. Ohly 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Outstanding Servicemen 1949 (Box 118)
    - List of Outstanding Servicemen, guests of Department of Defense 1950 Jan. (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Pageant Magazine 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Paul Palmer, Editor, Reader's Digest1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Wm. C. Parks 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Judge Robert Patterson 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Sedley Peck 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: O. E. Petersen 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Irving Pflaum, Chicago Sun Times1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Philippine Ambassador's visit 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Roxanna Pownall 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Robert H. Pritchard 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Norton G. Pritchett 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Mr. Potofsky 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with H. J. Procope 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Raymond S. Pruitt 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memos re: Paul Ramadier 1949-1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with J. Arthur Rank 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with G. P. Reed 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with H. L. Remmel 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Report of the Service Academy Board 1950 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: J. H. Retinger 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Major George Ribble 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Elizabeth Robinson 1949 (Box 118)
    - Memo re: Mr. Rogge 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with James Roosevelt 1949 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Sol. A. Rosenblatt 1949-1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with A. M. Rucker 1950 Sept. (Box 118)
    - Memo re: General Ruiz 1950 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence with Maharaja Jam Saheb of Nawanagar 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Carol O. Schmidt 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memorandum re: Secretary's Daily Calendar of Appointments 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Michael Shea 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Daniel M. Sheaffer 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Doctor W. M. Sheppe 1949-1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Charles Shreve 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Lieut. General Frank Simpson 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with J. J. Singh 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Helen Sioussat, CBS 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Spyros Skouras 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Harry Slattery 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with J. D. Small 1949 (Box 119)
    - Memorandum re: Sydney Small 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Arthur Clarendon Smith 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Millard F. Snider 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Benjamin Sonnenberg 1949 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Visit of S. African Ambassador 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Congressman Spence 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Harry Spratt 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with A. C. Spurr 1949-1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Sir Bertram Stevens 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Earl Stevenson 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Ingram Stainback 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Joe Starnes 1949 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Ernest Stauffen 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Col. Van R. Sternbergh 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Clarence Streit 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Robert A. Taft, Senator 1950 Sept. (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Olin Teague, Congressman 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Charles Allen Thomas 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Commander R. S. Thomas 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Louis B. Tim 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Col. Harry A. Toulmen 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Walter Trahan, Chicago Tribune1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with R. E. Truman 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with R. B. Tucker 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence re: Captain Vacheresse 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Arthur W. Vanaman 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Mrs. Robert Vaughn 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Tracy S. Voorhees, Under Secretary of the Army 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Doctor C. R. Wagner 1949 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Elmer Walker 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Col. James L. Walsh 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Thomas J. Ward 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Mark Watson, Baltimore Sun 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Thomas Watters 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with G. J. Watumull 1950 Sept. (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Wm. Webster 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Frank L. Weil 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Sumner Welles 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with R. H. White 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Robert W. White 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Westmore Willcox 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with A. N. Williams 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with T. J. Williams 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with E. A. Williford 1950 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Richard Wilson 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Dr. Robert E. Wilson 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Dr. R. A. Winnacker, Office of Secretary of Defense 1950 Sept. (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with William F. Wise 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Marrs Wiseman 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Walter B. Witherell 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with Harry H. Woodring 1950 (Box 119)
    - Rough draft, "The World Peace Act of 1950," and "The Leadership Emancipation Act of 1950" 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with General W. A. Worton 1950 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence with James H. Wright 1949 (Box 119)
    - Memo re: Wilson W. Wyatt 1949 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence re: Photographs, autographed photos, includes some personal notes, A-Z, 2 folders 1949-1950 (Box 120)
    - Correspondence re: Newspaper clippings, editorials, articles, cartoons, and television programs, A-E, 5 folders 1949-1950 (Box 120)
    - Correspondence re: Newspaper clippings, editorials, articles, cartoons, and television programs, F-Q, 11 folders 1949-1950 (Box 121)
    - Correspondence re: Newspaper clippings, editorials, articles, cartoons, and television programs, R-Y, 5 folders 1949-1950 (Box 122)
    - Correspondence re: Johnson's appointment as Secretary of Defense, A-B, 2 folders 1949 (Box 122)
    - Correspondence re: Johnson's appointment as Secretary of Defense, C-M, 11 folders 1949 (Box 123)
    - Correspondence re: Johnson's appointment as Secretary of Defense, N-Y, 9 folders 1949 (Box 124)
    - Correspondence re: the dinner in honor of Louis Johnson on March 28, 1949 1949 March-April (Box 124)
    - Correspondence re: the dinner in honor of Louis Johnson on March 28, 1949, Acceptances and Regrets, 2 folders 1949 March (Box 125)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: the dinner in honor of Louis Johnson, March 28, 1949 1949 March-May (Box 125)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: "Coffee Caucus," at the Army and Navy Club, March 29, 1949, for Louis Johnson 1949 March-July (Box 125)
    - Correspondence re: luncheon and dinner invitations from Secretary of Defense Johnson, A-W, 2 folders 1949-1950 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Nehru's dinner, Greenbrier Hotel, 5 folders (Removed and placed with series on India) 1949 June-1950 Jan. (Box 126)
    - Guest Lists, luncheon and dinner, of Secretary of Defense Johnson 1949-1950 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence re: clubs, club memberships, and requests to serve on special committees, B-W, 2 folders 1949-1950 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence re: letters of introduction for various people traveling abroad, B-J1949-1950 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence re: letters of introduction for various people traveling abroad, K-W1949-1950 (Box 127)
    - Correspondence: Louis Johnson's thank-you messages for copies of articles, books, and gifts, A-W, 2 folders 1949-1950 (Box 127)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Louis Johnson's visit to Creighton University for Commencement Exercises 1949 April-July (Box 127)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Louis Johnson's visit to Marietta College for Commencement Exercises 1949 April-July (Box 127)
    - Correspondence re: a proposed visit to New York University 1950 Feb.-March (Box 128)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Louis Johnson's visit to the Pennsylvania Military College for Commencement Exercises 1950 Jan.-June (Box 128)
    - Correspondence and Papers re: Louis Johnson's visit to Villanova College for the Dedication of the Commodore John Barry Hall 1949 (Box 128)